<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
  <channel>
    <title>WITH GOD DAILY - Audio Devotional</title>
    <link>https://efficiencynerd.github.io/with-god-daily-podcast/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Daily audio devotional from Skye Jethani, automatically updated each morning.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <itunes:author>Skye Jethani</itunes:author>
    <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
    <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
      <itunes:category text="Christianity"/>
    </itunes:category>

    <item>
      <title>Ps 12: A Lesson in Gravity</title>
      <description>This devotional, drawing from Psalm 12, contrasts the insecure boasting and manipulative words of those lacking spiritual depth with the profound "gravity of soul" possessed by God and the righteous. True power, exemplified by Jesus' humble birth, stems from an authentic, weighty presence rooted in truth, which naturally influences others without needing theatrics or exaggeration.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BChristmas%2BPsalms_%2BPs%2B12%2BA%2BLesson%2Bin%2BGravity.m4a" length="15035082" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-26</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:40</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Ps 23: The Good Shepherd Arrives</title>
      <description>This devotional explains how the familiar image of God as a good shepherd, found in Psalm 23, finds its ultimate fulfillment in Jesus. Old Testament prophecies foretold a righteous king, the "Good Shepherd," who would rescue God's lost and straying people from neglect and sin. Jesus' birth, announced to shepherds, declared him to be this long-awaited divine Shepherd, who came to lay down his life for his sheep.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BChristmas%2BPsalms_%2BPs%2B23%2BThe%2BGood%2BShepherd%2BArrives.m4a" length="14326874" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-25</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:19</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Ps 22: Never Abandoned by God</title>
      <description>This devotional explores Psalm 22 and Jesus' cry of abandonment on the cross, validating the universal human experience of questioning God's goodness and intervention during suffering. However, it ultimately affirms that God has not truly abandoned or hidden His face from the afflicted, but hears and cares, a truth powerfully demonstrated by the birth of Jesus at Christmas.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BChristmas%2BPsalms_%2BPs%2B22%2BNever%2BAbandoned%2Bby%2BGod.m4a" length="17950237" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-24</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>9:10</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Ps 21: Praising Power</title>
      <description>This devotional explains that psalms praising a king's power, like Psalm 21, are best understood as messianic prophecies, referring to Jesus Christ. Unlike corrupt human rulers, Jesus is the incorruptible King who will wield power righteously to establish God's rule. Therefore, we can trust and celebrate His coming as a leader beyond reproach.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BChristmas%2BPsalms_%2BPs%2B21%2BPraising%2BPower.m4a" length="12315564" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-23</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 10:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:17</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Ps 19: Ruler of Creation</title>
      <description>This devotional highlights that creation actively affirms God's glory and Jesus' identity, from His birth to His death, serving as more than just a backdrop. Jesus, the "second Adam," came to perfectly fulfill humanity's original calling to rule over creation in communion with God, a dominion the first Adam forfeited. Through His life and power, Jesus demonstrated this intended dominion, repairing the chaos of sin and revealing God's character within creation itself.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BChristmas%2BPsalms_%2BPs%2B19%2BRuler%2Bof%2BCreation.m4a" length="13853479" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-22</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:04</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Learning to Live with God Right Where You Are</title>
      <description>This devotional challenges the common misconception that fulfilling Christ's mission demands changing one's life circumstances or dedicating oneself solely to "sacred" church work. Instead, it emphasizes that God's expansive kingdom mission is lived out by welcoming heaven into our everyday vocations, relationships, and ordinary lives, right where we are. True discipleship means manifesting God's kingdom within our current circumstances, rather than abandoning them.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BLearning%2Bto%2BLive%2Bwith%2BGod%2BRight%2BWhere%2BYou%2BAre%2B1.15.12.m4a" length="16119297" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-19</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 10:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8:14</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Beware of Vampire Churches</title>
      <description>This devotional warns against "vampire churches" that drain members' spiritual life by treating them as resources for institutional goals, rather than empowering them for their broader callings. A healthy church, conversely, equips believers to deepen their relationship with God and manifest Christ's kingdom through their vocations and daily lives, fostering peace and joy. It's crucial to discern if a church cultivates true spiritual maturity and widespread impact, or simply consumes its members.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BBeware%2Bof%2BVampire%2BChurches%2B1.14.21.m4a" length="16957012" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 10:05:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8:39</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>How Big is God?s Mission?</title>
      <description>Daily devotional for Dec 17, 2025</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BHow%2BBig%2Bis%2BGod%27s%2BMission_%2B1.12.21.m4a" length="15096850" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-17</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 10:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:42</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>A Pyramid Without a Product</title>
      <description>This devotional warns that many churches, in their effort to "make disciples who make disciples," risk becoming like a "pyramid without a product" by failing to define what a true disciple is. This results in a self-perpetuating system that lacks spiritual substance, analogous to an illegal pyramid scheme. Such an approach, focused solely on growth without a clear "product," ultimately harms individuals and endangers the church's true mission.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BA%2BPyramid%2BWithout%2Ba%2BProduct%2B1.11.21.m4a" length="14586652" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-15</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 10:05:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:27</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>A Place to Wrestle</title>
      <description>This devotional explains that Christian faith involves a continuous "wrestling with God" over profound questions of meaning and purpose, acknowledging that doubt is inherent to the journey. Like Jacob, believers grapple with fear and uncertainty, but learn to trust God even when His plan isn't clear. The church provides a vital community where this spiritual struggle is shared, offering comfort and reaffirmation that God's justice ultimately prevails.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BA%2BPlace%2Bto%2BWrestle%2B9.28.20.m4a" length="12428610" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-12</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:21</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Essential Church</title>
      <description>A study found that personal spiritual disciplines, meaningful relationships, and serving others foster faith more than elaborate church programs or buildings. This calls the church to rethink its identity, shifting from a programmatic institution to a Spirit-driven, relational community essential for individual spiritual formation and God's mission in the world.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BThe%2BEssential%2BChurch%2B11.27.20.m4a" length="13243910" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 10:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:46</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Character or Charisma?</title>
      <description>This devotional argues that much of American Christianity, influenced by an "Evangelical Industrial Complex," has strayed from biblical standards by prioritizing marketplace acumen and charisma over spiritual maturity and character in its leaders. Consequently, leaders are often selected for their ability to generate revenue rather than their capacity to genuinely shepherd the flock, leaving believers vulnerable to ungodly influence and the dangers of a business-driven faith.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BCharacter%2Bor%2BCharisma_%2B11.24.20.m4a" length="13581517" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-09</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 10:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:56</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Peril of Visionary Churches</title>
      <description>This devotional critiques the modern church's business-influenced concept of "vision" as a leader's strategic plan, explaining that biblical "vision" refers instead to God's divine revelation. Adopting the worldly definition dangerously elevates human leaders and their ideas above Christ, who alone is the true spiritual unifier of a Christian community.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BThe%2BPeril%2Bof%2BVisionary%2BChurches%2B11.23.20.m4a" length="15713558" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-08</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 10:05:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8:01</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Problem With ?You?</title>
      <description>This devotional emphasizes that many New Testament letters were written to "us" (the church) rather than just "me," despite modern English translations using a singular "you." Our cultural individualism often leads us to misinterpret these communal instructions as solely personal commands, misapplying scripture and overlooking our corporate identity in Christ. Therefore, we must consciously consider how biblical teachings apply to our community, not just ourselves, to truly understand and live out our faith.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BThe%2BProblem%2BWith%2B%27You%27%2B11.13.20.m4a" length="14873231" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-05</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:05:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:36</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Best of Enemies</title>
      <description>This devotional cautions against the cultural tendency, even among Christians, to define ourselves and our faith through anger, contempt, and the demonization of "enemies." It asserts that true Christian faith, exemplified by the early church, should instead be motivated by Christ's unifying love and the cross, where Jesus sacrificed himself for his adversaries. Believers are called to release hatred and find their definition in God's love, not in division or animosity.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BBest%2Bof%2BEnemies%2B11.12.20.m4a" length="14570051" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-04</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 10:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:26</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Enemies No More</title>
      <description>Amidst deep societal division, this devotional emphasizes that a true Christian community is defined by its ability to reconcile former enemies and reflect God's unity. The spiritual key to achieving this is actively praying for the blessing and well-being of our opponents, a transformative practice that heals our own hearts, fosters reconciliation, and serves as the church's most powerful weapon against evil.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BEnemies%2BNo%2BMore%2B11.11.20.m4a" length="12635138" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-03</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 10:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:27</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Middle Voice</title>
      <description>Many Christians experience disillusionment because faith, when practiced as either relentless activity or passive waiting, often fails to transform lives. The devotional argues that true spiritual transformation occurs in the "middle voice," a collaborative and communal process where individuals, the church, and God actively participate and act upon one another. This relational and cooperative approach fosters genuine growth and heart change within a supportive community.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BThe%2BMiddle%2BVoice%2B11.10.20.m4a" length="13623266" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-12-02</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 10:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:57</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Jesus Bus</title>
      <description>This devotional challenges the idea of church leaders assembling a "bus" of the "right people," reminding us that the church belongs to Jesus. He intentionally brings together diverse individuals, even those with opposing views, demonstrating that true spiritual unity comes solely from abiding in Him, not from shared backgrounds, politics, or values. Therefore, Christians must examine if they are trying to dictate who belongs, or if they are truly on Jesus' inclusive bus.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BThe%2BJesus%2BBus%2B11.6.20.m4a" length="12826117" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-28</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 10:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:33</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Pure Thanksgiving</title>
      <description>This devotional challenges believers to examine their motives for gratitude, distinguishing between manipulative thanksgiving offered with an ulterior motive for future blessings and a purer form. It argues that true gratitude, exemplified by the one leper who returned to Jesus, seeks nothing in return and focuses on the Divine Giver himself, rather than merely the gifts received. Christians are thus encouraged to cultivate a selfless appreciation for God, the ultimate Source of all blessings.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BPure%2BThanksgiving%2B11.26.20.m4a" length="11782207" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-27</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 10:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:01</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>11:00 Sunday Morning</title>
      <description>The devotional challenges the church for often reflecting and reinforcing societal divisions through its racial homogeneity, rather than courageously overcoming them. It contrasts this with Jesus, who intentionally united a diverse group of disciples?like a Zealot and a tax collector?solely through their shared faith in Him, prioritizing this beautiful unity over pragmatism. Therefore, the church must embrace such Christ-centered diversity within its own walls if it hopes to play any role in healing the divisions of the world.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2B11_00%2BSunday%2BMorning%2B10.30.20.m4a" length="13953183" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-21</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:07</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Uncritical Currents of Culture</title>
      <description>The church's fundamental purpose is to preview God's kingdom by actively transcending and healing societal divisions, uniting diverse people into a new household of faith, rather than reinforcing worldly customs. Christians are called to intentionally examine their cultural values and practices, ensuring they embody Christ's vision of a unified community rather than unknowingly betraying it by perpetuating divisions.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BThe%2BUncritical%2BCurrents%2Bof%2BCulture%2B10.29.20.m4a" length="16165138" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>8:15</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>An Unworldly Strength</title>
      <description>This devotional contrasts Jesus' unworldly strength, forged in prayer and manifesting as love even for his enemies, with the world's fearful, combative power. It challenges the modern church, often operating out of fear with worldly weapons, to instead emulate Christ. Through prayer, the church can transform its fear into faith and anger into love, accessing divine strength to reflect Jesus' character.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BAn%2BUnworldly%2BStrength%2B10.28.20.m4a" length="14884822" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-19</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 10:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:36</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Church Finds a Way</title>
      <description>Daily devotional for Nov 18, 2025</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BThe%2BChurch%2BFinds%2Ba%2BWay%2B10.27.20.m4a" length="13797616" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-18</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 10:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:03</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Master  Slave</title>
      <description>Daily devotional for Nov 17, 2025</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BMaster%2B%26%2BSlave%2B10.26.20.m4a" length="13642038" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-17</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:58</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Intent Behind the Instruments</title>
      <description>This devotional highlights that true Christian worship, as exemplified by King David, transcends external rituals, music, or temples. God primarily desires a broken spirit and a contrite heart?a genuine relationship?rather than mere performance or mechanical offerings. External acts of worship are only meaningful when they express this deeper desire for God's heart.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BThe%2BIntent%2BBehind%2Bthe%2BInstruments%2B10.23.20.m4a" length="14755066" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-14</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 10:06:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:32</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>An Oasis of Beauty</title>
      <description>Daily devotional for Nov 13, 2025</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BAn%2BOasis%2Bof%2BBeauty%2B10.22.20.m4a" length="14156600" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-13</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 10:05:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:14</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Worship, Beauty, Justice</title>
      <description>This devotional argues that a consumerist, utilitarian mindset often infects Christian worship, leading us to see God and people as valuable only if useful or transactional. Instead, true worship should embrace beauty and "impracticality" to counteract this impulse and remind us that God and all humanity are to be adored. This adoration, expressed through valuing what isn't useful, is the essential prelude to pursuing justice for the oppressed and neglected.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BWorship%2C%2BBeauty%2C%2B%26%2BJustice%2B10.21.20.m4a" length="15293106" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-12</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 10:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:48</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Worship</title>
      <description>This devotional highlights the difference between transactional and genuine worship, using the example of the woman anointing Jesus. It teaches that true Christian worship is an impractical, beautiful act of adoration, motivated by love for God's intrinsic worth rather than practical utility or personal gain. Genuine worship flows from a heart captivated by God's beauty, pouring out our highest value as a pure expression of devotion.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BBeautiful%2BWorship%2B10.20.20.m4a" length="13095353" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-11</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 10:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:41</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Don?t Worship Like a Pagan</title>
      <description>This devotional contrasts pagan mythologies, where humans serve gods out of necessity, with the biblical truth that God is self-sufficient and does not *need* our worship or offerings. It argues that viewing worship as a transaction?offering praise to receive blessings?is a pagan mindset, not true Christianity. Instead, proper Christian worship is a non-transactional act of adoring God as an end in Himself, finding spiritual fulfillment in simply gazing upon His beauty and discovering His reciprocal adoration for us.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BDon%27t%2BWorship%2BLike%2Ba%2BPagan%2B10.19.20.m4a" length="13265983" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 10:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:46</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>A Nonsensical Gesture of Love</title>
      <description>This devotional argues that authentic Christian worship is a "nonsensical gesture of love," spontaneously offered to God from an encounter with His holiness, rather than a pragmatic calculation of personal gain or institutional growth. It challenges modern tendencies to approach worship with marketplace metrics, urging believers to embrace a selfless delight in God that transcends utility and feedback.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BA%2BNonsensical%2BGesture%2Bof%2BLove%2B10.16.20.m4a" length="15154807" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-07</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 10:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:44</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Ground Control, We Have a Problem</title>
      <description>Drawing from the experience of astronauts who needed to pause for cosmic reflection, this devotional emphasizes that Christians require intentional rest and meditation, particularly through Sunday worship. This practice allows us to gain God's perspective on our lives and work, fostering spiritual renewal and communion rather than solely focusing on relentless activity. Ultimately, it calls for a rhythm of mission and meditation to maintain a proper perspective on ourselves, our calling, and our Lord.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BGround%2BControl%2C%2BWe%2BHave%2Ba%2BProblem%2B10.15.20.m4a" length="11729754" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-06</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 10:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>5:59</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>No Rest for the Weary</title>
      <description>This devotional emphasizes the spiritual call for pastors to act as true shepherds by actively providing rest and restoration for God's people, as depicted in Psalm 23. It criticizes how the contemporary church often mirrors societal work addiction, inadvertently demanding more labor from congregants and contributing to burnout and church dropout rates instead of offering genuine sabbath. Therefore, the church must prioritize creating space for rest to truly care for its flock.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BNo%2BRest%2Bfor%2Bthe%2BWeary%2B10.14.20.m4a" length="12872729" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-05</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 10:05:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>6:34</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Why Not Saturday?</title>
      <description>The Old Testament Sabbath, rooted in Israel's deliverance from Egyptian slavery, symbolized freedom from bondage, a principle Jesus demonstrated by healing on the Sabbath to liberate people from suffering. For Christians, this ultimate freedom was achieved through Christ's resurrection on Sunday, transforming the Sabbath into a mission to seek deliverance for all people from every form of spiritual and physical bondage.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BWhy%2BNot%2BSaturday_%2B10.13.20.m4a" length="15195230" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotion-2025-11-04</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:09:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>7:45</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/efficiencynerd/with-god-daily-podcast/main/artwork.png"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Why Sunday?</title>
      <description>Daily devotional for Nov 3, 2025</description>
      <enclosure url="https://wgd-media.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/Church_series/WITH%2BGOD%2BDAILY%2B-%2BWhy%2BSunday_%2B10.12.20.m4a" length="0" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">devotional-2025-11-03</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 01:05:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>10:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
